Finding Aid for Michigan Prison Newsletters, 1969-1991
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
1969-1991
Michigan Prison Newsletters
94161 Ca.4b 2
Scattered issues of newsletters produced at Michigan prisons.
1 linear feet
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
Chiefly from the records of the American Friends Service Committee, Michigan Area Office (donor 4997 ) with materials from other donors added.
The collection is open without restriction.
The Michigan Prison Newsletters collection contains scattered issues, not complete runs, for most of these titles.
Subjects:
Prison periodicals.; Prisoners' writings, American--Michigan.; Adrian Temporary Correctional Facility (Adrian, Mich.)--Periodicals.Periodicals.; Cassidy Lake Technical School--Periodicals.Periodicals.; Charles E. Egeler Correctional Facility (Jackson, Mich.)--Periodicals.Periodicals.; G. Robert Cotton Regional Correctional Facility (Jackson, Mich.)--Periodicals.Periodicals.; Michigan Dept. of Corrections--Periodicals.Periodicals.; Brooks Regional Correctional Facility (Muskegon, Mich.)--Periodicals.Periodicals.; Florence Crane Women's Facility (Coldwater, Mich.)--Periodicals.Periodicals.; Hiawatha Temporary Correctional Facility (Kincheloe, Mich.)--Periodicals.Periodicals.; Huron Valley Men's Facility (Ypsilanti, Mich.)--Periodicals.Periodicals.; Huron Valley Women's Facility (Ypsilanti, Mich.)--Periodicals.Periodicals.; Ionia Temporary Facility (Ionia, Mich.)--Periodicals.Periodicals.; Kinross Correctional Facility (Kincheloe, Mich.)--Periodicals.Periodicals.; Lakeland Correctional Facility (Coldwater, Mich.)--Periodicals.Periodicals.; State House of Corrections and Branch of State Prison in Upper Peninsula--Periodicals.Periodicals.; Muskegon Correctional Facility (Muskegon, Mich.)--Periodicals.Periodicals.; National Lifers of America--Periodicals.Periodicals.; Offender Aid and Restoration of Oakland County--Periodicals.Periodicals.; Prisoners' Progress Association--Periodicals.Periodicals.; Riverside Correctional Facility (Ionia, Mich.)--Periodicals.Periodicals.
- Prison Newsletters
  - Adrian Temporary Correctional Facility
    - Adrian Bulletin, 1991 (Box 1)
  - Cassidy Lake Technical School, Chelsea
    - Format, 1981-1982 (Box 1)
  - Charles Egeler Facility, Jackson
    - Egeler News, 1988-1991 (Box 1)
  - Cotton Facility, Jackson
    - Cotton Focus, 1988 (Box 1)
  - Dept. of Corrections
    - Dialogues, 1978-1984 (Box 1)
    - Signal, 1988-1990 (Box 1)
  - E. C. Brooks Regional Facility, Muskegon
    - Guardian, 1991 (Box 1)
  - Florence Crane Women's Facility, Coldwater
    - Insight, 1988-1991 (Box 1)
  - Hiawatha Temporary Correctional Facility, Kincheloe
    - Insider, 1990 (Box 1)
  - Huron Valley Men's Facility, Ypsilanti
    - Huron Valley Monitor, 1986-1987 (Box 1)
    - Valley West, 1986 (Box 1)
  - Huron Valley Women's Facility, Ypsilanti
    - Determined Action for Women Now, 1982-1990 (Box 1)
  - Ionia Temporary Facility
    - Recreation Rap Sheet, 1988 (Box 1)
    - Temporary Times, 1988-1989 (Box 1)
  - Kinross Correctional Facility, Kincheloe
    - Link, 1990-1991 (Box 1)
      (2 folders)
  - Lakeland Correctional Facility, Coldwater
    - Lakeland Pen, 1991 (Box 1)
    - Untitled, 1988 (Box 1)
  - Marquette Branch Prison
    - North Star, 1989 (Box 1)
    - Weekly Progress, 1969 (Box 1)
  - Muskegon Correctional Facility
    - Factor, 1986-1991 (Box 1)
  - National Lifers of America, Huron Valley Women's Facility, Ypsilanti
    - Minutes and reports, 1982 (Box 1)
  - National Lifers of America, Jackson
    - Newsletter, 1987 (Box 1)
  - Offender Aid and Restoration of Oakland County, Pontiac
    - Oar-Deal, 1982-1988 (Box 1)
  - Prisoners' Progress Association, Jackson
    - In Struggle, 1978-1979 (Box 1)
    - Inside Out, 1975-1978 (Box 1)
  - Riverside Correctional Facility, Ionia
    - Riverside Voice, 1978 (Box 1)